Wait... this isn't my dorm.
Rough cloth, mildew, cobwebs... where the hell am I?
This... this isn't my face.
Lin Wan'er. A noble's daughter, made an imperial consort —
then framed for witchcraft and locked in the cold palace. Three years.
My lady! Madam Liu's here — on the Empress's orders. They've come to kill you!
Presenting Madam Liu—
Consort Lin, the Empress is merciful. She'll let you die in one piece. Do be grateful.
I can't fight them. Begging's useless...
Did I cross over just to die all over again?
Host near death. Demon Bloodline — force-activating.
What are you—
Minor demon "Madam Liu" slain. EXP +10.
Demon Bloodline is now Level 1.
From now on, nobody decides whether I live or die.
Madam Liu... was a demon?