The seventh day after Cui Wei's death — new faces appeared outside the cold palace.
My lady, plain-clothes men are lurking out there — too steady to be eunuchs. Trained fighters.
How many?
Three to five, in shifts. Two by day, three by night — they only watch from afar.
The Emperor's men.
The Emperor? Why would His Majesty watch you?
Because — he fears me.
A deposed concubine who can suddenly kill demons. If you were Emperor, wouldn't you fear her?
He won't strike — he needs me more than he fears me. He can't deal with the demon kings at the border.
He fears me, but he needs me more. So he sends watchers — not killers.
My lady — what should we do?
Nothing.
We do nothing. Train. Eat. As long as I don't reach for the throne, he won't move.
Xiao He — find out when I might be granted an audience with His Majesty.
You wish to see the Emperor, my lady?
Yes. I have a deal to offer.
I am done surviving in the cold palace. The demon kings at the border are my offering.
And the Emperor — is my pawn.
Wait and see. Soon — this palace will know who its true master is.
The hunter of the cold palace has turned her gaze — toward the throne.