After Cuiwei, the Empress says nothing. She's cutting losses.
One pawn dies, send another. She'll never admit she planted demons.
Bloodline LV2. EXP 195/500. 305 to next level.
Big gap. First — master what the python gave me.
Once, this was a killing banquet. Now, it's her training ground.
Frost Control.
Go.
Not sharp enough yet.
One afternoon — from five scattered to ten on target. That's the Demon Progenitor's blood.
Next: ice wall.
Defense — good enough. Holds an hour. No more fear of ranged attacks.
The python's dead — its books are mine. And they hide demon secrets.
So that's why I got Frost. But cross-attribute refining backlashes — for others.
Myriad-Demon Bloodline has no counter. Others' wall is my open road.
Tucked into the last page — not a technique. A way out.
Xuantian Pavilion hides the Calm-Heart Pill formula — it suppresses backlash. The python wanted in too.
To enter, I need the Emperor's trust. The border — a thousand-year tiger demon.