Madam Liu didn't bleed — she burst into black smoke. Everyone saw it. Everyone kept quiet. That's how a demon dies.
I need time — time to figure out what's inside this body.
Myriad-Demon Bloodline System. Level 1. Warning: if your demon awakening tops 50%, you lose your mind — for good.
Refining Madam Liu's leftover demon blood... Done. EXP +10.
Jade Demon Rank unlocked. Body +100%, Speed +80%, Senses +50%. New skill: Demonic Aura.
Okay, that's just ridiculous.
Demonic Aura — on.
That black cat out back? Lowest-tier spirit. The woman in the west wing — human.
Three of them under the locust tree... and something big at the bottom of that well.
The cold palace is a hunting ground. The fallen concubines? They're the prey.
No wonder they keep "dying of illness" and vanishing.
My lady... you look amazing today.
Get some sleep tonight. Whatever you hear — don't come out.
My lady, what are you going to do?
Hunt demons.