Midnight — that's when they come out to feed.
Mmm, this cat meat is so tender.
Finish up. We've got "rent" to collect in the east court — Lady Zhang's turn this month.
"Rent"? They collect lives like rent.
Well, if it isn't Consort Lin. Your blood smells far sweeter than hers.
Wait... she smells like a demon. A strong one.
A washed-up concubine? A demon? Please.
This... this is impossible...
Who's first? Or all at once?
Too slow.
3 minor demons slain. EXP +30. Demon blood refined — 80/100.
Still 20 short...
I know you're down there. Come up. Let's talk.
A discarded concubine with ancient demon blood... and she comes alone? Bold.
Century-old serpent demon. Silver Rank, early stage. Threat: high.
Devour you, and I might become a dragon. A banquet, two nights from now. Will you come?
I'll come.
See you then, Consort Lin.
A trap dinner? I'll show this snake who the real hunter is.