Demon Bloodline... activated.
Wait... this isn't my dorm.
Coarse cloth, mildew, cobwebs... where am I?
The face in the mirror... that isn't me.
Lin Wan'er — a minister's daughter, made imperial consort,
framed for witchcraft, cast into the cold palace. Three whole years.
My lady! Madam Liu is here —
on the Empress's orders, to send you to your death!
Presenting Madam Liu—
Consort Lin, the Empress is merciful — she grants you a whole corpse.
You ought to be grateful.
I can't fight them, begging is useless...
Did I cross over just to die all over again?
Host near death — Demon Bloodline, force-activating.
Your... your eyes?!
Minor demon "Madam Liu" slain. EXP +10.
Demon Bloodline is now Level 1.
From this day on, no one decides whether I live or die.
Madam Liu... was a demon.
So how many more are hiding in this cold palace?