The fox demon Hu Sanlang — had not gone far.
As she left the banquet — he stepped out from behind a tree.
My Lady — wait.
I forgot one thing.
What thing?
Three silver needles between his fingers — tips glowing blue. Poisoned.
The formula is real — but its final ingredient, only one person in this kingdom has.
Who?
The Empress Dowager.
Qingxin Pill needs Thousand-Year Cold Iron — hidden in her chambers.
So this formula — is no formula at all?
At least you know what you need. How to get it — that is yours.
What do you really want?
I want — you to owe me a favor.
Kill Zhao Tieyi for me — and I am yours from then on.
You can't even beat me — what use are you to me?
I can't beat you — but I steal, I listen, I lay traps. You don't.
Fine — Zhao Tieyi, after I return from the borderlands.
My thanks, my Lady!
One more thing.
The Empress has brought a Fifth-Rank Demon Master into the palace — for you alone.
I know.
The fox demon — dissolved into red smoke.
My lady — are you all right?
How strong must one become — to be free of every threat?
My lady is already very strong.
Not enough. Far from enough.
Three months — they will be here in three months at most.
Three months — from Silver Rank to Gold Rank, and beyond.
The fastest way — kill demons. Refine more demonic blood.
Tomorrow morning — I will see the Emperor.
My lady wishes to see — His Majesty?
Yes. The demon kings of the border won't wait. Neither will I.
She clenched her fist — dark-gold patterns emerged on her arm, gleaming cold in the moonlight.
This blade — is ready to be drawn.