Zhao An delivered the report last night — every word like a needle in his heart.
Thirteen demons. A Hundred-Year Snake Demon. Ancient demonic blood. A Second-Rank Master.
A Second-Rank Master — one against a hundred on the battlefield.
And Lin Wan'er — the deposed concubine I exiled myself — wields such power?
What unsettles me more is six words — "ancient demonic blood".
If a human carries demonic blood — is she human, or demon?
Zhao An — did your men see her kill?
The agents only saw the remains, Your Majesty — thirteen carcasses.
One was a six-meter Hundred-Year Snake Demon — its skull shattered by a single punch.
What else has she done?
She bound several minor demons as spies. And practices a frost art — ice spears that strike from ten paces.
Tell me — could she one day, do this to me?
Your Majesty — do not make her your enemy yet. Used right, she is a blade.
And if she cannot be used?
Then strangle her — before she grows beyond reach.
I need a blade. But a blade too sharp — will cut its wielder.
Keep watching her. And investigate another — Lin Huaiyuan.
I want to know what "strange ones" he met in the south.
Also — issue the order. In three days, I shall inspect the cold palace myself.
I will see with my own eyes — what this Lady Lin has become.
He took the edict from the hidden compartment — read it long — then locked it away again.
Lin Wan'er — do not force my hand.
In three days, the Emperor walks into the cold palace — to see whether she is human, or demon.