Three days after the python died, the Empress sent her real one.
Lady Lin — by Imperial Edict, you're summoned to Kunning Palace.
My lady... Matron Li never comes here. This is bad.
If I don't go, she'll have her excuse. Let's see what she's got.
She wants to crush me with pageantry? I'll dress better than she expects.
From the cold palace to her hall — every step up the power ladder.
Forbidden-art residue detected. Nature unknown. Marked.
No demonic aura here... but something else is.
Lady Lin. Long time. I almost forgot the cold palace still housed you.
So many died in there — and yet you look livelier than ever?
How did Madam Liu die? Who killed those demons?
Demons? I'm a frail woman, Your Majesty. How could I?
Good. Lady Lin — you've grown so much sharper.
Matron Li. Send someone to attend her in the cold palace.
Your servant Cuiwei greets the lady. — Mid-tier demon. Stronger than Liu.
My lady! The Empress's gift... is a demon?!
I keep her — at least I know what she is. And she'll lead me back to the Empress.
[Dead silence — a shadow stands at the door — no breath]
She doesn't strike. She just listens. — She's gathering intel.
Then watch all you want. I've got nothing but patience.