After the fox demon left, Shen Nian didn't rush to the Emperor.
She went back to the dry well first.
You... came back again.
I need to refine something here.
A hundred-year snake demon — mediocre quality.
But for you right now — it's enough.
The moment the cold liquid touched her palm —
[Refinable demon blood detected. Refine? Yes / No]
Yes.
An icy force surged from her palm.
Demon Bloodline boiling — dark-gold patterns emerged.
The Demon Emperor bloodline is indeed dominant.
Ice complements you — your Frost Mastery will rise a tier.
The snake's qi was cold and savage — a viper raging within.
The Demon Bloodline a tiger — devouring every drop.
The Seal Maiden rose — pressed a small hand to her brow.
A golden rune — flowed into Shen Nian's brow.
Thank you.
Don't talk — focus.
[Refining complete. Ice shards 1→20, Ice wall 5 inches]
[New skill "Ice Seal" — freeze 3 zhang ground for 5 breaths]
Ice shard pierced stone 3 inches deep — frost spread around.
More than double the power.
Silver-rank demon mid-tier — barely safe in the palace.
But against a real Demon King — you can't even flee.
I know. That's why I'm going — to the frontier.
A thousand-year Tiger Demon — to ascend to Gold-rank.
Thousand-year Tiger Demon — Gold-rank mid-tier.
You're only Silver-rank early — two tiers short.
If you go — you'll die.
Who says I'll fight head-on? I'm human — not demon.
Humans can borrow blades, set traps, use poison.
The Seal paused — then her lips slightly upturned.
Interesting. Of every Demon Emperor heir I've seen —
you are the most cunning.
That's called — wisdom.
What do you want then? A book?
Bring a person.
Who?
The Seal didn't answer — became a statue again.
Back above ground — dawn was breaking.
The eastern sky paled — the palace took shape.
Shen Nian stood by the well — and drew a deep breath.
A new day — a new beginning.