The fox demon was gone — but she did not leave.
She lifted her cup, scanning every corner of the garden.
The fox demon was gone — but something else was watching.
— Come out.
A black silhouette emerged from behind the broken rockery.
Who are you?
He said nothing — he only lifted the fox demon's empty cup and breathed in.
Hu Sanlang — owes me a life.
You hold a grudge against him?
No. What he owes — will be repaid in time. But tonight — I came for you.
He lifted his head — a pair of dull grey-white eyes, like two clouded glass orbs.
Lady Lin — the blood of the Demon Ancestor flows in you. The word has spread.
Not only the demons of this palace — but those beyond, now know.
Who spread it?
Before he died — the Snake Demon told his kind. The demon kings of the southern range — know.
They are deliberating — whether to come eat you. Or come crown you.
Crown me?
Crown you as their king. The Demon-Emperor's bloodline — gives you the right.
But most want to eat you — and ascend.
The Demon Ancestor's blood — is a double-edged blade. Power. And countless eyes upon me.
Why tell me this?
Because I too am a demon. I do not wish to be devoured.
If you become the strongest — I will follow you.
You are blunt.
Demons do not lie.
Remember — your time runs short. Three months at most — and they arrive.
He spoke. He vanished into the dark.
Three months — to grow strong enough to face the kings of the southern range.
Or — become someone else's prey.
Looks like — I'll need to speed things up.
Emperor within. Seal below. Ten thousand mountains' kings beyond.
One goal remains: Gold Rank — by the fastest road.