That night, I didn't sleep. I wanted to
test it — this power I'd just taken. Was
it real?
I pictured the scales on Madam Liu's back,
that knack for swallowing one's footsteps.
The next instant I rose from the couch
without a sound, crossing the broken
shards — not a whisper.
Moonlight spilled in. I looked down — my
own shadow was three shades fainter than
my body. Stealth. It worked.
But when I reached again for that brute
force she'd had before turning to smoke,
my chest wrenched as if two hands tore it
apart. It hurt.
Same-origin rejection. One body holds but
a few arts at once; greed... brings
backlash.
I cut the thought at once. I've survived
this long never by greed. However defiant
this bloodline, it has its rules — what
you can swallow, you may not master.
So take only what matters, and grow
steadily. Eat one, grow one measure
stronger.
In the dead of night I threw on Madam
Liu's empty robe and, with my new stealth,
slipped out past the ruined walls of the
cold palace.
In the northwest corner stands an old
locust tree, three arms around. As I
neared, the dark-gold patterns beneath my
skin began to burn faintly — demonic aura.
Far thicker than by day.
Under the tree crouched three "people."
Dressed as palace maids, but their faces
had long ceased to be human.
One with a scale-covered face and
yellow-green vertical pupils; one with
twig-like fingers barbed at every joint;
the last, mouth split to the ears, baring
two rows of jagged teeth.
Tsk... the Li family's cat — tender meat.
Eat faster. Tonight we still collect rent
at the east court — Eunuch Liu said it's
Concubine Zhang's turn this month.
Rent. I remembered what Xiaohe told me by
day — Concubine Zhang of the east court
hadn't been seen in three months.
So it wasn't that she had vanished. She
had been taken as rent.
I didn't rush to act. I was counting:
three demons, each with its own art. But
tonight I can swallow only one — so choose
the one most worth keeping on my own body.
Gentlemen. This rent — on Concubine
Zhang's behalf, I'm calling it off.