The saddest one is Lady Zhang... something in that well dragged her away.
That ends now.
5 lesser spirits slain. EXP +5. Now 85/100.
Spirits barely give any EXP... still 15 short.
That's Consort Lin? She's like a whole different person...
Consort Lin, please — sit.
Thank you for having me.
I hear you killed Madam Liu, the Empress's envoy. They say she burst into black smoke.
She came to kill me. I only defended myself.
What I mean is — Consort Lin, you're no ordinary woman.
Demon energy rages; spirit energy is calm. Mask it well, and he'll never know.
I see... just an ordinary woman who's dabbled in breathing arts.
Hook, line, and sinker.
You hold your wine well, Consort Lin.
Let's call it a night. Allow me to walk you back.
I've changed my mind. That's not spirit energy — it's demon blood. Ancient. Powerful.
Devour you, and I'll finally become a dragon. Tonight is my night!
Here it comes.
A century of cultivation... perfect. I'll take it as my level-up.