The days passed in the cold palace. Mornings — frost training. Ten ice spears in a fan now.
Afternoons — the demon-blood manual. Nights — meditation.
Sometimes down the well — the Seal always says the same words: Come and take me.
Two ranks more — and the Seal closed her eyes again.
She dared not — the Ancient Demon King was too strong. Even approaching it might destroy her.
My lady — a letter arrived for the cold palace!
Tonight at midnight. Backyard. Demon banquet. Come or die.
Fox-musk. A fox demon.
He sent an invitation. To refuse would be cowardice.
Midnight. The backyard glowed with red lanterns — like a wedding.
Lady Lin — your reputation precedes you. I am Hu Sanlang. A pleasure.
A fiery-red fox tail trailed behind him. A fox demon.
Hu Sanlang. A friend of the Snake Demon?
No friend. He was a loser I never bothered to kill. You saved me the trouble.
Tonight — I came to do business.
I know you are seeking — the Qingxin Pill formula.
This is the real formula. Stolen from Xuantian Pavilion.
The pavilion has wards — I can only reach the first floor. Beyond that — sealed.
What do you want?
Help me — kill someone.
The Imperial Guard Captain — Zhao Tieyi. He slaughtered my family. I want his life.
Why not do it yourself?
He cultivates pure-yang arts — perfectly countering my demonic power.
I can help you — but only after I reach the Gold Rank.
I can wait. But promise me — after you kill him, give me his heart.
What for?
— To eat.
— Deal.
The fox demon bowed deeply — and dissolved into red smoke into the night.
The cold palace — keeps getting busier.
Her goal was now fixed: the Gold Rank of Demons.