The three minor demons turned back at
once. Blood from the dead cat still clung
to the scaled one's mouth.
Where did this discarded consort crawl out
from, talking so big?
Return the rent? Give us your flesh for a
midnight snack first!
I did not answer. I watched. The three
demons spread into a loose triangle; the
old locust stood behind them, and my only
retreat was the low wall at my side.
I could fight, but not for long. I only
had stealth; I could not borrow brute
strength. If I fought all three head-on, I
would not last ten breaths.
Then I would not fight head-on.
I lowered my eyes, and my figure faded
three shades into the tree shadow. The
split-mouth demon lunged first, fangs
wide, aiming for my throat.
I did not retreat. I stepped in. Stealth
swallowed my footsteps; it missed, and its
whole neck stretched out.
I slipped behind its neck, locked my
fingers around its throat, and used its
own momentum to drag it into the old
locust trunk.
Ah!
Thud. Two rows of jagged teeth shattered
loose.
Refine.
Demon body detected. Refine it?
Yes.
Black smoke surged from that torn mouth
and drilled through my fingers into my
blood. A vision exploded in my mind: it
could mimic human voices and speech.
Demon-devouring extraction. Ability
available: Voice Capture, Imitation
Speech.
Useless. Imitation was a hidden trick, a
deception. It would not help me establish
power now.
But the other two were already charging.
The scaled one growled, while the
twig-finger demon flanked from behind, its
barbs flashing under the moon.
There was only one thing I needed to stand
firm in this cold palace: the ability to
take a hit.
The instant the scaled demon slammed
toward me, I did not dodge. I turned past
the barbs and pressed my hand onto its
spine.
You are the one.
Demon body detected. Scaled demon. Scale
armor, hard defense.
Refine.
This time, I was greedy. The split-mouth
demon's voice craft had not yet settled,
and the scaled demon's armor flooded in
after it.
Two streams of demonic energy collided
inside me. My chest felt stuffed with a
red-hot coal, burning through blood and
bone.
Same-origin rejection. Bloodline overload.
Warning: greedy devouring backlash.
My vision went red. Not blood. The entire
imperial city was veiled in red gauze,
turning into flesh I should swallow.