Emperor Yongning. Ten years on the throne. The Empress within, demon kings without — and no one at court can fight.
Three years in the cold palace — no outside contact, no one taught her combat?
Confirmed, Your Majesty. Only the lowest scullion eunuchs who delivered supplies.
Then how does a powerless girl become this? ...The way she looked at me — like a different person.
Your Majesty, may I say what I shouldn't.
The fever night she almost died. By morning — she was reborn.
I suspect — she is not the Lady Lin who entered this palace.
Her father Lin Huaiyuan once traveled south — among strange people. Perhaps he left her a way to survive.
The year she arrived, she was sixteen. She blushed every time she saw me — and her smile had two dimples.
The one I see now — is a blade reforged. Too sharp to hold.
Keep watching her. Don't startle her. Report every move, every day.
[The hall doors close in silence — a candle pops — silence]
The Lady Lin in the cold palace — I find her pleasing. If you don't trust her, use her first.
Lin Wan'er, Lin Wan'er — what kind of person are you, really?
If Lady Lin shows treasonous intent — Captain of the Imperial Guard is to execute on the spot.
I can grant you power. I can take it back. Do not — disappoint me.