One moment she held the poisoned wine,
forcing me to thank her for my own death.
The next, she turns and runs.
Those eyes... you shouldn't have eyes like
that! Guards — help —
She knows it better than anyone: a deposed
concubine meant to die by poison should
never open eyes like these.
I'd taken half a step and was already
behind her. So fast it stunned even me —
this isn't my skill; a dark-gold heat is
moving my body.
My palm lands on her back. The feel is
wrong — not flesh, but cold tanned hide,
covered in fine scales.
Just as I thought. You're not human.
You little wretch! You've ruined
everything —
Demon body detected. Refine it?
Refine.
She shrieks, her body withering before my
eyes, dissolving into a roiling cloud of
black smoke — drawn inch by inch into my
palm.
No blood. Only a pool of bubbling, foul
liquid, and an empty dark-blue robe
collapsed on the floor.
Demon devoured, power seized. Gained:
false human skin — stealth.
Now I understand. This is no empty game of
leveling up. It's eating. Devour a demon,
take all it has — eat one, grow one
measure stronger, gain one art.
But the price comes at once. The heat
suddenly ebbs away, my whole body drained
hollow, my vision going black.
I catch the wooden couch to keep from
falling, cold sweat on my brow. Power
isn't free. One feeding — only one — at a
time.
The gold light withdraws from my eyes, my
phoenix eyes turning ordinary black again.
I look down at the foul pool still
bubbling on the floor.
Madam Liu... was a demon.
Then this cold palace that swallows people
whole — how many more lie hidden here?