Three days ago, one bite would've shattered her.
So you finally couldn't hold back?
You're not spirit energy... you're a demon! How are you THIS strong?!
So fast... I underestimated this she-demon.
Toxin detected. Demon blood auto-neutralizing.
Impossible! My venom drops even Golden Core cultivators!
That's the one spot on its body with no scales.
You wanted to eat me, didn't you? Go on. Eat.
Mercy! I'll submit — I can help you take down the Empress!
When you ate them, did you ever show mercy?
Great demon slain. Bloodline now LV2 — Silver Rank! Skill unlocked: Frost Control.
Mercy, my lady! I only steal scraps — I've never eaten anyone!
From today, you work for me.
From this day on, the cold palace has one master.
My lady... did you become a goddess?
Not a goddess. Something far more terrifying.