Consort Lin, Her Majesty is merciful. She
grants you an intact corpse. Thank her.
On my first day after transmigrating,
someone brought poisoned wine and ordered
me to die.
But the face in the bronze mirror... was
not mine.
Phoenix eyes, thin lips, a faint scar on
the left wrist. Memories rushed in. Her
name was Lin Wan'er, legitimate daughter
of a minister, a deposed concubine.
Three years ago, she was framed for
witchcraft and banished here. Three nights
ago, she died.
The original owner was already dead. Yet
the death edict still came as planned.
Meaning tonight was always meant to be her
death night.
Your Highness! Why are you up? Madam Liu
is here with the Empress's order!
Tonight... tonight they will send you to
your death!
Madam Liu arrives!
Consort Lin has suffered here for three
years. It is time to rest. Silk, dagger,
or poisoned wine. Choose one yourself.
Please show mercy, Madam Liu! Her Highness
is weak. She cannot bear this!
Shut up! Drag her away.
Fight back? This body could barely stand.
Beg? Lin Wan'er begged for three years,
and only this wine came for her.
Do not be afraid, Your Highness. Drink it.
It will not hurt.
Bitter almond scent. Poisoned wine. They
would not even give me time to cry.
At a time like this... why are you
smiling?
I am smiling because you are impatient. So
impatient you would kill a dead woman
twice.
Host near death. Ten Thousand Demon
Bloodline awakening.
The scar on my left wrist split open with
dark gold. Demonic patterns crawled
through my blood and bones.
Demonic aura detected. Can devour, refine,
and seize its art.
Your eyes... What are you?
Who I am does not matter.
What matters is this: from today on, in
this cold palace, I decide who lives and
who dies.
Madam Liu is a demon. How many more hide
in this man-eating palace?
Only now you know fear? Too late.