Day three. Time to test the spy.
Drop a hint at the well — "she glows at night when she meditates." Watch her.
Sister Cuiwei... my lady meditates every night, and her body... seems to glow.
Glow? ...What color of glow?
She must've turned to Buddhism — just chanting.
[A fingertip punches the paper window — one eye peers in]
Let her see — just not enough. That's how you bait.
Her eyes went red looking at you — like a starving wolf on meat!
"Health exercises"? Some wandering Taoist taught me. Nothing big.
She thinks I'm a mortal who grew demonic power. Tonight, she strikes.
My lady, I brought you a midnight bowl. — Midnight? How thoughtful.
Let me feed it to you. — So you finally couldn't hold back?
You... you're a demon too?!
Stronger than Madam Liu. Mid Jade-Rank... that's it?
The Empress sent us! One more in the imperial kitchen — "Madam Liu" — the strongest of us three.
Lesser demon Cuiwei slain. EXP +10. 195/500.
Imperial kitchen... Madam Liu. Time to switch rooms again.