She did not know — the Emperor had written two decrees for her. One reward. One death.
She only knew — one demon remained in the cold palace. Deep within the dry well.
Three days ago — beyond the stone bed, she sensed a thread of demonic aura.
Faint as a candle in the wind — yet its quality was staggering. A blade in its sheath.
Three days later — she was ready.
Xiao He — whatever you hear tonight, do not come out.
Guard the well. If I don't return in half an hour — go to the Empress Dowager.
The well dropped over ten zhang. She slowed her fall — landed soundlessly.
Bones. Rubble. The Snake Demon's lair — already stripped.
She walked past the stone bed — into a narrow passage choked with black moss.
A hundred paces in — the passage opened. An exquisite stone chamber.
Night-pearls in the walls — bathing all in soft gold. At its center — sat someone.
No — not someone.
You came.
The day the Snake Demon died — I knew. I have been waiting.
The blood of the Demon Ancestor runs in your veins. You are — the heir of the Demon Emperor.
I have waited here — three hundred years.
You may call me — the Seal.
I am no demon. I am a Seal placed by the Ancients — and inside, sleeps the real thing.
An Ancient Demon King. Sealed here — for three thousand years.
In a hundred years — it will break free.
Reinforce the Seal — or, devour its power.
With Demon-Emperor blood — you can consume any demon's strength.
Devour it before it wakes — and you become, the new Demon Emperor.
The new Demon Emperor… I need time to think.
There is no rush — I will wait.
When she climbed out — the night had grown deep.
My lady — what's down there?
— A secret.
From this night on — her goal is no longer the cold palace. It is the throne of all demons.